

Contact

- **618 282 62 94**
- aasanchezlazcano@gmail.com
- www.github.com/adanlazcano
- in www.linkedin.com/in/adanlazcano
- Durango, MX.

Education

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science ITA Durango

Technical Skills

5 HTML	
 CSS	
Js JavaScript	

Node Is

React.Js

PHP PHP

C Sharp

Git

Languages

Spanish

English

Profile

Full-Stack Developer with over 10 years experience, I consider myself a person who likes challenges and problem solving. I love self-taught learning and I consider that I have a high sense of commitment and responsibility, I am used to working for objectives and taking on the challenges that arise. I consider myself a person with a good attitude and I am currently looking for new projects that will lead me to greater job growth.

Experience

Universidad de

Web Developer

I participated with a team of developers belonging to the systems department of the University of Guadalajara, I did the process of generating records for the students of the University Center for Administrative Economic Sciences (CUCEA) such as CENEVAL, social service report, report of professional practices and professional exam, making the previous process more efficient, which consisted of manually performing said report in a text editor, currently the module is in production and allows you to generate the report by category, consult the report at any time list of minutes per student, reducing the time that this process lasted.

2015-2020 **PLANINCORP**

OUTSOURCING company dedicated to offering subcontracting services for several important companies in JALISCO, QUERETARO, LOS CABOS, MONTERREY and various states of the country. In which I had the opportunity to work on various innovation projects of some systems that were already obsolete, their corresponding analysis was carried out and work was carried out on various management systems (PAYROLL, INVOICING, STAFF, PURCHASING AND CUSTOMER MANAGEMENT). I had the opportunity to participate in one of the most important projects of the company which, with a billing system of more than 60 thousand stamps on a monthly, I was working on the implementation of the updates to the SAT guide for payroll and billing. The innovation that was carried out in various systems, the working hours of the employees were reduced, since normally the payroll area had very heavy days in which many overtime hours were performed, it was possible to reduce the time in which they worked various processes in the company's management systems.

2013-2020

Web Developer

I participated in various projects in a Freelance way, for example: Design and development of web pages, Shopping cart, Sales of technology software. Develop the ability to work for objectives and achieve a greater organization in my time, I developing projects on time to clients.

2008-2013 Secretaría de

Training staff in software management issues (Office automation, C# Programming, Web Programming). Preventive and Corrective Maintenance of hardware and software. Generation of reports and statistics, Monitoring, System maintenance /development, IT project innovation strategies, Database management and optimization, Testing and error correction. Various projects were carried out which were successfully concluded, thus achieving that the processes that were handled manually and took too much time, could be carried out through a system and speed up times, as well as having the information at the time it is needed. quickly and easily.

Interest







